ukincorp.co.uk 2015-12-14

# Company Start-Up Agent - Legal Disclaimer

**Agency**

We accept orders and instructions only on the basis that those instructing us do so as principals and are liable directly to us for payment of our account.

**Adequacy of Instructions**

We provide services only on the basis that those instructing us give us all proper, necessary and timely instructions, authority and information (including the execution of all documents required) to enable us to undertake lawfully and effectively the business instructed, and indemnify us accordingly.

**Privacy Policy**

Coddan is committed to protecting your privacy and will only use the information that we collect from you lawfully (in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998).

We do not use 'spam' which we define as random emails to personal email addresses where the recipient has not been a customer of ours. This privacy policy explains how we use the information we collect about you, how you can instruct us if you prefer to limit the use of that information and procedures that we have in place to safeguard your privacy.

**The Information We Collect and How We Use It**

If you choose to pay online, your credit card information is collected directly by WorldPay (http://www.worldpay.co.uk) and is neither accessed by us nor stored on our servers.

When you apply to incorporate a company or register for any of our services we need to know your name, postal address, e-mail address and telephone number. We also need to know additional details including names, addresses, dates of birth and some further information relating to certain individuals who may be appointed as officers and/or shareholders of companies we are instructed to incorporate on your behalf.

We gather this information to allow us to process your company registration, process any orders you may make and notify Companies House of the appointments of various persons in the normal course of our business as company formation agents. The relevant information is then used by us, our agents and sub-contractors to provide you with statements of your account maintain the appropriate public records at Companies House as required under the terms of the Companies Act and to communicate with you on any matter relating to the conduct of your account and the provisions of the service in general.

We may also use aggregate information and statistics for the purposes of monitoring website usage in order to help us develop the website and our services and may provide such aggregate information to third parties. These statistics will not include information that can be used to identify any individual.

From time to time we may provide your information to our customer service agencies for research and analysis purposes so that we can monitor and improve the services we provide. We or our agents and sub-contractors may contact you by post, e-mail or telephone to ask you for your feedback and comments on our services.

**Your Consent**

By submitting your information you consent to the use of that information as set out in this policy. If we change our privacy policy we will post the changes on this page, and may place notices on other pages of the website, so that you may be aware of the information we collect and how we use it at all times. We will also e-mail you should we make any changes so that you may consent to our use of your information in that way. Continued use of the service will signify that you agree to any such changes.

Owing to the global nature of the Internet infrastructure, the information you provide may be transferred in transit to countries outside the European Economic Area that do not have similar protections in place regarding your data and its use as set out in this policy. However, we have taken the steps outlined above to try to improve the security of your information. By submitting your information you consent to these transfers.

In addition to registration we may ask you for personal information at other times, for example when you enter a competition or promotion run or sponsored by Coddan and when you report a problem with one of our sites or services. If you contact Coddan we may keep a record of that correspondence. Coddan also occasionally asks users to complete surveys that we use for research purposes. Whenever Coddan collects personal information we try to include a link to this Privacy Policy on the page in question.

Your responses help us to sell appropriate advertising space and so minimise the cost of our services to you - or even provide some of them at no charge at all. They also enable us to personalise services to our readers.

Coddan uses cookies as a means of offering and providing customisable and personalised services. However, your browser has settings that will allow you to accept all cookies, be informed as cookies arrive or reject all cookies. The downside of rejecting all cookies is that we are then unable to match the site content we offer you to what we know about your preferences from your previous visits. In addition, advertising networks that serve ads onto Coddan sites may use their own cookies.

Coddan collects IP addresses for system administration, for independent audit and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. By this we can see how our sites are being used, for example, what services and facilities are popular, and how long users spend on particular pages. This is data about our users' browsing actions and patterns and it does not identify anyone individually.

When you telephone a Coddan company, or someone who is dealing with calls on our behalf, we may record the conversation to ensure the security of any transaction discussed, to help us to review our quality of service and to assist in the training and development of the employees who take such calls.

**How Does Coddan Use My Information?**

Coddan's primary goal in collecting personal information concerning subscribers is to provide them with a customised experience of our site. By knowing a little about you, Coddan is able to deliver more relevant advertisements and content to you, and by demonstrating the quality of our users we are able to secure advertising funding which keeps down the costs to the users.

When delivering targeted advertisements, Coddan acts merely as the middleman. Advertisers give us an advertisement and tell us the type of audience they want to reach (for example, design specialists, or pump buyers in process industries). We take the advertisement and display it to users meeting the relevant criteria.

Coddan undertakes research on our users' demographics, interests and behaviour based on the information provided to us upon registration, during a promotion, from our server log files or from surveys. We do this to better understand and serve you, the user. This research is compiled and analysed on an aggregated basis. Coddan may share this aggregated data with advertisers or business partners. We will use our best endeavours to ensure, where reasonable, that our business partners and advertising customers have effective on-line privacy policies and are registered under the Data Protection Act (as all of our relevant businesses are).

**Collection of Data**

When you are on a Coddan site and are asked for personal information, you may not be sharing that information with Coddan alone. Some services are offered jointly with a partner company. In order to provide this co-branded service to you, it is necessary for us to share your personal information with those partner companies.

Promotions and competitions that run on Coddan's sites may be sponsored by companies outside the Coddan Group or may be co-sponsored by us and another company. Some or all data collected during a promotion may be shared with the sponsor.

Please be aware that Coddan advertisers or web sites that have links on our site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those web sites linked to Coddan are not covered by this privacy statement.

**With Whom Does Coddan Share My Information?**

Coddan and its associated companies are prohibited by virtue of the Data Protection Act 1998 from disclosing any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or under the circumstances described below. The following describes some of the ways that your information may be disclosed.

**Business Partners & Sponsors**

We may disclose your personal information to business partners or sponsors, but this is drawn to your attention prior to data collection. Some or all data collected during any Coddan promotions may be shared with a sponsor. If personally identifying data about you will be shared, we will tell you when we collect the data.

**Online Purchases**

If you make a purchase from a site hosted by Coddan, the information obtained during the purchasing transaction, and the information you give such as your credit card number and contact information, is provided to the merchant concerned. This is to enable transactions to take place. You agree that Coddan and its associated companies have no responsibility or liability for any such independent store privacy policies.

From time to time, you may be offered the opportunity to receive materials or special offers from selected third parties. If you opt-in to receive information from these third parties you are giving us permission to share your name and email and/or physical address details with them.

**Third Party Data**

Coddan may also disclose account information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating Coddan's Terms, Database Rights or Copyright or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) Coddan's rights or property, other Coddan users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.

**Collection, Use and Distribution of Your Information**

Coddan or its sponsors or business partners may, from time to time, contact you regarding their products and services.

On some types of Coddan promotions, we will ask for your email address in order to update you on your score, entries and status. When you participate in these types of promotions, you automatically receive promotion-related email. Sometimes these promotion-related email messages may include targeted advertisements.

From time to time Coddan does rent or sell user information to other reputable organisations as permitted under the Data Protection Act 1998. If you do not wish to allow your data to be shared, you can choose not to use a particular service, not to participate in certain promotions or contests, or you can select to opt out of your information being shared on the registration page.

No data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed entirely secure. While we strive to protect your personal information, Coddan can neither ensure nor warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.
